Hello it's Scott Manley here.
你好 我是斯科特-曼利
Today I want to talk to you about a little bit of local history for me.
今天我想和你们谈谈我的一段地方历史
And well it's linked to the US space program of the 1960s and 1970s
它与美国20世纪60年代和70年代的太空计划有关
so I occasionally go kayaking out of a place in Sausalito
所以我偶尔会去索萨利托的一个地方划皮划艇
and in that area there's a building that's currently being destroyed(restored)
在那个地方 有一座建筑目前正在被摧毁（修复）
and on the side it says machine shop.
边上写着机械车间
It was well the machine shop for the Marine shipbuilding division of W. A. Bechtel company
它是W.A.Bechtel公司的海洋造船部门的机械车间
generally shortened to marine Ship
一般简称为海洋船舶
and during World War II this shipyard was stood up in a matter of months.
在第二次世界大战期间 这个船厂在几个月内就建立起来了
So that it could build ships for the war effort.
这样它就可以为战争建造船只
In the few years that are operated it built almost 100 tankers and freighters and supply ships.
在运营的几年里 它建造了近100艘油轮、货轮和补给船
Now after the war most of these ships would be retired or placed in reserve fleets
战争结束后 这些船大部分都退役了 或者被列入后备船队
but in the 1960s three of these would be brought out of storage
但在20世纪60年代 其中三艘被从仓库中取出来
and rebuilt as tracking ships for the Apollo program.
并被重建为阿波罗计划的追踪船
And these would become the USNS Redstone Vanguard and Mercury
这些船将成为美国海军红石号先锋号和水星号
but they weren't the first ships the US built to track rockets.
但它们并不是美国建造的第一艘用于追踪火箭的船只
So the US has operated tracking ships for rockets since like 1950.
因此 美国从1950年起就开始运营追踪火箭的船只
This was the bumper test of the V2 where there were sub-orbital launches
这是V2的大丰收测试 有亚轨道发射
and they flew these over the Atlantic
他们把这些东西飞过大西洋
so to track them they borrowed a pair of destroyers
所以为了追踪它们 他们借了一对驱逐舰
and they pretty much used their like fire control radar and optical systems to track the hardware.
他们几乎是用他们的火控雷达和光学系统来追踪这些硬件
But the first time the dedicated set of tracking ships were stood up
但是 第一次建立专门的跟踪船是为了开发 "斯纳克 "号
was for the development of the Snark cruise missile
是为了开发 "斯纳克 "巡航导弹
so this was a cruise missile that would have a range of about 5500 miles.
所以这是一种巡航导弹 射程约为5500英里
And in the testing it would carry it over thousands of miles of the Atlantic ocean
在测试中 它将带着它穿越数千英里的大西洋
before it reached final target tracking station.
然后才到达最终的目标跟踪站
Now if anything went wrong in that thousands of miles of empty no ocean
现在 如果在这几千英里的空旷海洋中出现任何问题
they would have had a very hard time to figure out what really went on there.
他们将很难弄清那里到底发生了什么
So to fill this literal gap they got six ships from the ready reserve fleet.
因此 为了填补这个文字上的空白 他们从预备役舰队中得到了六艘船
Ships which had been built for use in World War II and then they modified them to be tracking ships.
这些船是为第二次世界大战建造的 然后他们把它们改装成追踪船
So these were like small freight supply ships.
所以这些就像小型货运补给船
They were 54 meters long and about 550 tons.
它们长54米 大约550吨
The army had built hundreds of these as small ships to supply troops in the field.
军队建造了数百艘这样的小船 为战场上的部队提供补给
They weren't even given names.
它们甚至没有被赋予名称
They were just given numbers.
它们只是被赋予号码
So when the air force took control,
所以当空军控制了这些船后
they were given simple call signs from the phonetic alphabet echo through kilo.
他们被赋予了简单的呼号 从拼音字母的回声到公斤
And they give them the antennas and the other tracking equipment for their mission
他们为他们的任务提供天线和其他跟踪设备
and they would spend weeks at sea to collect like 15 minutes worth of telemetry as the missiles flew past them.
他们在海上花了几周的时间来收集导弹飞过时的15分钟的遥测数据
So anyway after that the next batch of tracking ships that were developed by the US
因此 在那之后 美国开发的下一批跟踪船
were for the bigger rockets that would actually go into space.
是为那些真正进入太空的大型火箭开发的
Things like the Thor the Atlas and the Titan.
像雷神号、阿特拉斯号和泰坦号
So this group of ships were converted from the larger C1 cargo ships
所以这批船是由较大的C1货船改装的
and they were about like they were twice as long like 120 meters 4000 tons
它们的长度是原来的两倍 大约是120米 4000吨
and two of these would actually end up ultimately after sort of evolution
其中有两艘在经过某种演变之后最终
being assigned to project Mercury specifically.
被分配给水星项目
This would be the USNS Rose Knot and the Coastal Sentry
这将是USNS玫瑰结号和海岸哨兵号
and they would get extra equipment to allow them to actually send commands to the spacecraft.
他们将得到额外的设备 使他们能够真正向航天器发送指令
They wouldn't be passive observers.
他们不会是被动的观察员
So like previous satellite experiments hadn't really needed continuous communications
所以像以前的卫星实验并不真正需要连续的通信
but for project Mercury NASA's medical experts
但对于水星项目 美国航空航天局的医疗专家
they wanted the flight surgeons to have continuous availability throughout the orbit.
他们希望飞行外科医生在整个轨道上有持续的可用性
So they came up with a network of tracking stations around the world
所以他们想出了一个由世界各地的跟踪站组成的网络
and mostly in friendly countries and territories.
而且大多在友好国家和地区
Bermuda, the Canary Islands, Nigeria, Zanzibar, Australia, Mexico.
百慕大 加那利群岛 尼日利亚 桑给巴尔 澳大利亚 墨西哥
but in the oceans they had to fill those gaps the Atlantic the Pacific and the Indian Ocean.
但在大洋上 他们必须填补这些空白 大西洋、太平洋和印度洋
So they put ships to cover this.
因此 他们投入了船只来填补这一空白
Now these ships were expected to actually operate independently from mission control, right.
现在 这些船被期望实际独立于任务控制中心运作 对吧
The stations on land could send signals via landlines to mission control and get feedback
陆地上的站点可以通过固定电话向任务控制中心发送信号并获得反馈
but the ships out at sea couldn't guarantee that they would be able to contact shore.
但在海上的船只不能保证他们能够联系到岸上
They might be able to get radio messages through
他们也许能够通过无线电信息
but they certainly couldn't send the real-time telemetry.
但他们肯定无法发送实时遥测信息
so every ship would have a small team dedicated to them with like capcom and flight surgeons.
因此 每艘船都会有一个小团队专门负责他们 比如说Capcom和飞行外科医生
Now John Glenn was actually the capcom on the Coastal Sentry
现在 约翰-格伦实际上是 "海岸哨兵 "号上的通讯员
for the final flight of the Mercury program
在水星计划的最后一次飞行中
supporting Gordon Cooper on a mission which would last 34 hours.
在一次持续34小时的任务中支持戈登-库珀
Now because of that duration being so long
现在 由于时间如此之长
not every tracking site would be able to communicate for every single orbit.
不是每个跟踪点都能在每个轨道上进行通信
And when the flight started having technical problems on the 19th orbit
而当飞行在第19个轨道上开始出现技术问题时
the only ground stations in the position to communicate with him were Hawaii and Zanzibar.
唯一能与他联系的地面站是夏威夷和桑给巴尔
The Coastal Sentry was in the correct place in anticipation of re-entry
沿海哨兵站在正确的位置上 期待着重返大气层
but because of the technical issues
但由于技术上的问题
they needed to come up with a new re-entry checklist and Glenn had to communicate that
他们需要制定一个新的再入大气层检查表 格伦必须与之沟通
and then one hour later as Gordon Cooper was trying to manually fly the re-entry
然后一小时后 当戈登-库珀试图手动驾驶重返大气层的时候
John Glenn gave him the countdown and the mark to activate the retro thruster.
约翰-格伦给了他倒计时和启动反向推进器的标志
Okay so flash forward a few years and it's the Gemini program.
好了 再往前推几年 就是双子座计划了
And again the Rose Knot and the Coastal Sentry are operating.
而玫瑰结和海岸哨兵也在运行
They've been upgraded a little but they're still very much autonomous mission control systems.
它们已经被升级了一点 但它们仍然是非常自主的任务控制系统
Now during the drama of Gemini 8
现在 在双子座8号的剧情中
they were both in a position to communicate with the capsule during those orbits
它们在那些轨道上都能与太空舱进行交流
when the stuck thruster caused the spacecraft to enter a rapid uncommanded roll.
当推进器被卡住导致航天器进入快速非指令性滚动时
They worked with the crew on the last few orbits
他们在最后几个轨道上与机组人员合作
as emergency situation forced the mission to be cut short
因为紧急状况迫使任务缩短
and new re-entry plans had to be made and communicated to the crew.
并且必须制定新的再入计划并传达给机组人员
So anyway that said the first group.
所以无论如何 这说的是第一组
There's another group of tracking ships that were converted
还有另一组被改装的跟踪船
and these were made from the larger VC2 or Victory Class ships.
这些是由较大的VC2或胜利级舰艇改装而成的
So these are larger still than the C1 hulls that the Rose Knot is.
所以这些比玫瑰结号的C1船体还要大
So there's like nine of these I think.
所以我想有9艘这样的船
They were acquired various times by various programs
它们在不同时期被不同的项目收购
but I think most of them ended up supporting the Pacific missile range and in particular the Corona program.
但我认为它们中的大多数最终都支持了太平洋导弹发射场 特别是科罗娜计划
We have rockets going up and capsules coming back down
我们有火箭升空 太空舱降落
but a couple of these ended up being used to support NASA's human space flight program
但其中有几个最终被用来支持NASA的载人航天飞行计划
so actually yeah the Range Tracker was also used in Gemini
所以实际上是的 测距仪也被用于双子星计划
but the Watertown and the Huntsville those were actually upgraded to work as Apollo tracking ships
但Watertown号和Huntsville号实际上被升级为阿波罗追踪船
with they were used for the re-entry and recovery in the Pacific.
它们被用于重返大气层和在太平洋的回收
So now that brings me to the three ships practically built in my backyard.
因此 现在让我来看看这三艘几乎是在我家后院建造的船
These are larger still.
这些都是更大的
They're based on T2 tankers.
它们以T2油轮为基础
now these tankers were 160 meters long
现在这些油轮有160米长
and they would displace over 2000 tons when full of oil.
当装满油时 它们的排水量将超过2000吨
There were about 500 of these built to supply US fleets during World War II.
在第二次世界大战期间 大约有500艘这样的油轮用于供应美国舰队
I mean to get an idea of how fast these were built
我是说为了了解这些油轮的建造速度
there's one example in Marine that was built in 33 days from keel laying to sea trials
海军陆战队有一个例子 从铺设龙骨到海试只用了33天
so the specific type that was used for conversion was the T2-SE-A2
所以用于改装的具体型号是T2-SE-A2
which were exclusively built by the Marine ship yards.
这些都是由海洋造船厂专门建造的
These were distinguished over the others by having improved engines
这些船的特点是拥有改进的发动机
which delivered something like 35% to 40% more power than the more common versions.
比普通版本多出35%到40%的动力
Now many of these ones were named for the fortified missions
现在 这些船中有许多是以强化的传教士命名的
which were established in California by order of the king of Spain in the 18th and 19th century.
在18和19世纪 根据西班牙国王的命令在加利福尼亚建立的
The mission San Juan would become the Mercury.
圣胡安传教团将成为水星号
The mission De Pala became the Redstone
德帕拉传教所成为红石号
and the mission San Fernando became the Vanguard.
而圣费尔南多传教所则成为先锋队
And of course since you're all space fans you can see the theme behind those names right.
当然 由于你们都是太空迷 你们可以看到这些名字背后的主题吧
The modified ships would be 21 meters longer at a total of 181 meters.
改造后的飞船将长21米 总共181米
But they didn't simply cut them in half and add an extra chunk of hull in the middle.
但他们并不是简单地把它们切成两半 并在中间增加一大块船体
They actually cut out the entire midsection of the ship which was mostly fuel tanks.
他们实际上切掉了整艘船的中间部分 其中大部分是燃料罐
They took only the bow and the stern and then built an entirely new midsection.
他们只取了船头和船尾 然后建造了一个全新的中段
The modified vessels they included like a whole bunch of large steerable dish antennas above the deck.
改造后的船只 他们在甲板上安装了一大堆大型可转向碟形天线
They supported sending and receiving and radar.
他们支持发送和接收以及雷达
They had a suite of electronics below deck including like computers right.
他们在甲板下有一套电子装置 包括像电脑一样的东西
They had all the equipment necessary to send commands to the vehicles and decode the telemetry.
他们有所有必要的设备来向车辆发送指令和解码遥测数据
Like the ships that supported Mercury in Gemini they had been built with the notion
就像支持双子座水星的飞船一样 它们在建造时就有这样的想法
that they could operate as standalone mission control stations
它们可以作为独立的任务控制站运行
independent of the primary mission control in Houston.
独立于休斯顿的主要任务控制
However in the intervening years satellite technology had developed quite quickly
然而 在这几年中 卫星技术发展相当迅速
and by the time these were operating the ships actually had pretty reliable satellite uplinks
到了这些飞船运行的时候 实际上已经有了相当可靠的卫星上行链路
which provided like bi-directional relay between the ship systems and mission control in Houston
它在飞船系统和休斯顿的任务控制之间提供双向中继
so the on-board autonomy that they had been built with
所以它们在建造时的机载自主权
was never really needed when they were actually operating in the Apollo program.
当它们在阿波罗计划中实际运行时 并不真正需要
But you know to be clear these weren't just dumb satellite relays.
但你要知道 这些并不只是愚蠢的卫星中继
One interesting and important system that set them apart from the land-based tracking stations
有一个有趣而重要的系统使它们与陆基跟踪站不同
was the ship's position and measuring system or SPAMS
是船舶的位置和测量系统或SPAMS
which in many ways resembled the inertial navigation hardware used on spacecraft
它在许多方面类似于航天器上使用的惯性导航硬件
and it could be used to determine the ship's position to within about 100 meters
它可以用来确定船舶的位置 大约在100米之内
and that in turn allowed them to determine the spacecraft's position to a similar precision.
而这反过来又使他们能够确定航天器的位置达到类似的精度
So they would have one tracking ship that would be positioned
因此 他们将有一艘跟踪船 将被定位在
so that it could track the completion of the translunar injection burn
以便它能够跟踪平流层喷射燃烧的完成情况
and then that would be able to instantly provide independent measurements of the injection trajectory
然后 它将能够立即提供独立的喷射轨迹测量
to make sure that the vessel was in fact on the correct course for the moon.
以确保该船实际上是在通往月球的正确路线上
And figure out what kind of course corrections would be needed to get there according to plan
并计算出需要什么样的路线修正才能按计划到达那里
and for Apollo 11 this job was given to the Mercury.
对于阿波罗11号 这项工作交给了水星号
But all of this it really just served to confirm the reliability of the onboard systems
但所有这一切实际上只是为了确认机载系统的可靠性
and after the success of Apollo 11 most of the ships stopped being used.
在阿波罗11号的成功之后 大部分的飞船都停止了使用
The Redstone the Mercury and Huntsville weren't used for future launches after Apollo 11.
红石号、水星号和亨茨维尔号在阿波罗11号之后没有用于未来的发射
And they were all returned to the reserve for other uses.
它们都被送回储备库用于其他用途
Only the Vanguard remained as the Atlantic tracking station needed for immediate post launch support.
只有 "先锋 "号仍然作为大西洋跟踪站 需要在发射后立即提供支持
And it performed the job for all the launches in of the Saturn rockets
它为土星火箭的所有发射执行了这项工作
all the way through Apollo skylab and of course Apollo–Soyuz.
一直到阿波罗太空舱 当然还有阿波罗-联盟号
Technology had basically made the dedicated tracking ships largely redundant.
技术基本上已经使专门的跟踪船在很大程度上成为多余的了
Like improved onboard systems on the rockets meant that they are the spacecraft
就像火箭上改进的机载系统意味着它们是航天器的一部分
meant that they needed less ground control.
意味着他们需要更少的地面控制
And as the equipment itself got smaller there was less need to devote an entire ship to it.
而且随着设备本身变得更小 也就不需要把整艘船都用在这上面
And of course US spacecraft in orbit began to use communication satellites
当然 美国在轨航天器开始使用通信卫星
which means that they didn't have to worry about ground station visibility all the time.
这意味着 他们不必一直担心地面站的能见度
So eventually all the tracking ships involved in Mercury, Gemini and Apollo have been scrapped.
因此 最终所有参与水星、双子星和阿波罗的跟踪船都已经报废
I mean some have had limited careers after this after their role in the space race.
我的意思是 有些人在太空竞赛中发挥作用后 此后的职业生涯也很有限
Vanguard actually worked on the development of submarine navigation systems in the 1980s
Vanguard公司实际上在20世纪80年代就从事潜艇导航系统的开发工作
and it was still doing stuff in 1998 when it was retired.
而且它在1998年退役的时候还在做事情
And in 2013 it eventually made its last voyage to Brownsville Texas to be scrapped
而在2013年 它最终在德克萨斯州的布朗斯维尔进行了最后一次航行 被报废了
just down the road from where Spacex has been making lots of more scrap metal.
就在Spacex一直在制造大量废金属的路上
There is one tracking vessel that's still pretty recognizable
有一艘追踪船仍然很容易辨认
but it wasn't involved in any of the human space flight missions.
但它并没有参与任何人类太空飞行任务
The Vandenberg was built as a troop carrier in Richmond California
范登堡号是在加州里士满作为运兵船建造的
again pretty close to me.
离我也很近
And in the 1960s it was converted to track missile tests
在20世纪60年代 它被改装为跟踪导弹试验
specifically measuring the re-entry dynamics of warheads.
特别是测量弹头的再入动力学
And in the late 1990s it was actually used for the movie Virus.
在20世纪90年代末 它实际上被用于电影《病毒》的拍摄
It was redecorated to look like a russian research ship
它被重新装饰成俄罗斯研究船的样子
but finally in 2009 it was intentionally sunk near Key West to form an artificial reef.
但最终在2009年 它被故意沉入基韦斯特附近 形成一个人工礁
It would become a tourist attraction for sports divers to explore
它将成为一个旅游景点 供运动潜水员探索
and of course for marine life to call home.
当然也是海洋生物的家
I'm Scott Manley. Fly safe.
我是斯科特-曼利 飞行安全